degreeguideonline.com 2013-05-23

# DegreeGuideOnline.com

Personal Information: Your personal information is important to us. Any personal information you share with Online Education, including your name, mailing address, phone number, email address or any other personal information will be stored securely and encrypted so that a third party cannot capture, read or access that information while it is transmitted between your computer, Online Education and shared with any service providers helping provide you with competitive quotes. We may also share personal information with other third parties to administer our business or to provide related services and as otherwise permitted or required by law. Our privacy practices will always comply with applicable Federal and State laws.

| 

Links to Other Websites: Our site contains links to other websites and DegreeGuideOnline.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of these third-party websites. You should always read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policy may differ substantially from ours. Please make note that when you click on one of these links you will be directed to another website

Cookies: Cookies are small text files saved on your computer's hard drive while your browser is running. Online Education will not to use cookies to track, collect, or store your personal information. However, we may use cookies to help make it easier for returning users to complete one of our insurance quote forms. If you would not like to accept cookies, you can easily change your browser settings to prevent cookies from being stored and still visit Online Education.

Tracking Pixels: Some pages on Online Education may contain electronic images known as tracking pixels or single-pixel GIFs. These pixels may collect certain types of non-personally identifiable information, such as a visitor's cookie number, time and date of a page view, the visitor's referring URL and a description of the pages they visit. The information collected using these pixels does not identify individual users.

Online Education is committed to the security of your financial and personal information. Our servers and data processing operations are in a secure environment protecting your account information from being accessed by third parties.

Notification of Changes: Online Education may edit this privacy and security policy from time to time. When we make any substantial changes we will notify you by posting a prominent notice in our privacy policy or on our home page. You will always be able to opt out. To opt out, please contact us.
